## PREFERRED WIX MAK

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## 0450 250 848



makwaiyeung@hotmail.com



Southbank



www.linkedin.com/in/wai-yeung-mak

## PROFILE

As a dedicated and responsible computer science graduate with excellent time management, teamwork, and communication skills, I consistently complete tasks on time. My expertise in front-end development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, and React Native allows me to create engaging and visually appealing user interfaces.

## SKILLS

## **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE:**

Intermediate:

· Javascript, HTML, CSS

Foundational:

• Python, C#, C++

#### **FRAMEWORK**

Intermediate:

· React, React-Native

Foundational:

· Express, Node

#### **TOOLS / UNDERSTANDINGS**

Intermediate:

· Git, Jira, Figma, Restful API

#### Foundational:

 PowerBI, Tableau, Docker, CICD, MySQL, MongoDB, SDLC

## EDUCATION

#### **BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE**

**DEAKIN UNIVERSITY** 

- · Graduated with Distinction
- STEM scholarship receiver

## HIGHER DIPLOMA IN GAME SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

HONG KONG INSTITUTE OF VOCATIONAL EDUCATION

03/2021 - 11/2022

Burwood, Melbourne

01/2018 - 12/2020

08/2022 - 09/2022

Hong Kong

#### PLACEMENT

#### **DEVELOPER PROGRAMMER**

Strong Compute Sydney

- Tested MLPerf AI benchmarks with different models like 3D-unet, rnnt and resnet. We achieved 80%-90% benchmarks
- Utilized Docker and VM that allows testing the benchmarks remotely

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **ANALYST PROGRAMMER**

03/2023 - 05/2023

**GS1 Hong Kong** 

Hong Kong

- Developed a program for data transformation and yielding with Python and Pandas which allowed my manager to achieve data visualization
- · Adjusted and fixed PowerBI report for internal use and was successful on developing the new UI
- · Participated in frontend development with Next.js which enabled us to present demos to various customers
- Setup Gitlab E.g. Gitlab runner, CICD pipelines to help our team deploy and maintain the project in an efficient manner

<u>JUNIOR PROGRAMMER</u> 10/2021 - 01/2022

Technine Hong Kong

- Project involved: JPEX Crypto Asset Platform
- · Developed both website and app by using React which improved UI and gained the customer's satisfaction
- Worked with a large team including back-end team, and UI designer to increase the project's efficient by 30%

## UNIVERSITY PROJECT

#### **TEAM LEADER & FRONTEND DEVELOPER**

Deakin university (DataBytes)

03/2022 - 10/2022 Burwood, Melbourne

- · Project in charged: Discount-Mate
- Developed website and mobile application by React-Native and React so it achieved a cross-platform feature
- · Developed a basic application and admin board system which achieved our target and able to demo
- · Analysed model and method for data prediction with data team and came up with the concept
- · Focused on leadership and teamwork skills then the lecture gave me an HD for this project

## OTHER EMPLOYMENT

#### **FOOD SERVICE PROVIDER**

06/2022 - 01/2023

**POKED** 

CBD, Melbourne

- Served a section with over 50 customer capacity during lunchtime.
- · Prepared Food in the morning
- Provided suitable customer service, For example, took an order, addressed customer problem, cashier

#### **FOOD SERVICE PROVIDER**

11/2022 - 01/2023

Boss Man Food Group

CBD, Melbourne

- · Served a very large group of customers in Winter Night Market.
- · Prepared and Cooked food for the order
- · Provided a range of customer service. For example, took an order, cashier

#### FRONT HOUSE STAFF

London K Burgers

09/2022 - 12/2022

Kensignton, Melbourne

- · Prepared Food and made milkshake during duty
- Provided customer service such as receiving phone call orders, and chatting with customers.

## LANGUAGE

Mandarin Cantonese Fluent Native

## ACTIVITIES

#### **INNOFES (DEAKIN UNIVERISTY)**

Project Leader

- Pitched Discount-Mate project to professionals in IT industry
- Prepared mobile application prototype

## REFEREES

Available on request